// Question Types
// 1. MCQs | Multiple Choice | single
// 2. boolean | true/false | single
// 3. MAQs | Multiple Answers | multiple

import { Topic } from '.'

export const Q029: Topic = {
  topic: 'TOEIC Part 5',
  level: 'Beginner',
  totalQuestions: 10,
  totalScore: 10,
  totalTime: 100,
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'The Premier Membership Plan is our most popular program, but ------ are worth considering.',
      choices: ['something', 'another', 'each', 'others'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['others'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'All the information you need to properly maintain your new machine ------ in the instruction manual.',
      choices: ['will provide', 'is provided', 'provided', 'have been provided'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['provided'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'To ensure high production quality, ------ maintenance of the machines is very important.',
      choices: ['periodically', 'periods', 'periodic', 'periodicals'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['periodic'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'The management of Croyell Manufacturing is very pleased with the company’s steady ------ and increasing revenues.',
      choices: ['growth', 'grow', 'grown', 'grew'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['growth'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'This year’s annual meeting was ------ well attended that we need to consider changing to a venue with a larger capacity next year.',
      choices: ['too', 'such', 'very', 'so'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['so'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'The results of this customer satisfaction survey were almost consistent with past ------.',
      choices: ['found', 'find', 'findings', 'finds'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['findings'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'The main ------ of this notice is to ensure that all employees make efficient use of resources in the workplace.',
      choices: ['experience', 'objective', 'confirmation', 'choice'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['objective'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'More ------ ways to acquire new clients will be discussed at tomorrow’s sales meeting.',
      choices: ['effectively', 'effective', 'effectiveness', 'effect'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['effective'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'Ms. Alonso demonstrated exceptional solution skills when ------ with difficulties.',
      choices: ['confronts', 'confront', 'confronting', 'confronted'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['confronted'],
      score: 1,
    },
    {
      question: 'You must sign up three days in advance at the ------ to receive individual counseling on dietary issues.',
      choices: ['late', 'later', 'lately', 'latest'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswers: ['latest'],
      score: 1,
    },
  ],
}